

# Anup Chandra Mondal

Team Player | Dedicated | Inquisitive

+8801710415952

anupmondal6970@gmail.com

Dhaka, Bangladesh 💽

linkedin.com/in/anup-mondal-bba6a0200/in

github.com/Anup-Mondall50/



#### **About Me**

Data Scientist with 1+ years of broad-based experience in building data-intensive applications, overcoming complex architectural, and scalability issues in diverse indudtries. Proficient in predictive moddeling, data processing, and data mining algorithms, as well as scripting language, including Python and Java.

#### **Skills**

- Probability & Statistics
- Programming, Packages and Softwares (Python, Java, TensorFlow etc.)
- Creativity
- Data Wrangling
- Cloud Computing (AWS, Azure, Google Cloud)
- DevOps

# **Expertise**

- Statistical analysis and computing
- Machine Learning
- Programming
- Deep Learning
- Processing large data
- **Mathematics**
- Big Data

### **Achievements**

- Participated in ICPC 2021 Dhaka Regional contest.
- Solved more than 200+ problems in various online judges

### **Work Experience**

6 month

#### 2022-present Data science & Big Data |Internship

Datasoft Systems Bangladesh Limited

- An understanding of programming languages, such as Python, R, and
- The ability to visualize data by using such data science tools as Tableau and PowerBI.
- · An understanding of how to use machine learning to collect data and develop predictive models.
- A grasp of software frameworks, such as Hadoop, for processing big data. And Also understand Teamwork, Communication, Problemsolving

2021-present

l years+

#### Solve a Data Science Project| Kaggle Project

- Customer Churn Prediction: In business "churn" represents the rate at which customers stop doing business with an entity. Because of its relevance to companies churn prediction is used in many industries (telco, bank, etc).
- Text Classification: Text classification consists of assigning predefined categories to free open-ended text.

#### **Education**

2019-2023

**B.Sc. in Computer Science & Engineering** 

**Daffodil International University** 

4 years

CGPA:3.65

2017-2019

H.S.C.(Science)

2 years

Jahangirpur Govt. College

GPA:4.50

2015-2017

S.S.C.(Science)

2 years

Mohadevpur Sarba Mongala (Pilot) High School

GPA:4.32

#### **Interest**

Artificial Intelligence, Video Games

## Reference

#### **Dil Afroz Begum**

Director, Admin & Human Resource,

Datasoft **Phone:** 880-2-48115029 Email: info@datasoft-bd.com